Guide to the George Washington University, Office of Student Life records, 1915-2014 RG0115
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Posters, 1998-2006; RG0115 Series 28; 5 Linear Feet; 1 Linear foot (Map-folder 1)
  - NCAA Elite 8 women's basketball, undated; Series 28 (Map-folder 2, Poster 2)
  - Welcome Week Your History in the Making [cartoon poster], undated; Series 28 (Map-folder 2, Poster 3)
  - Welcome Week '98, 1998; Series 28 (Map-folder 3, Poster 1)
  - Black History Celebration, 1992 January 30 - March 12; Series 28 (Map-folder 3, Poster 2)
  - Get Carried Away..., Undated; Series 28 (Map-folder 3, Poster 3)
  - The Fine Art of Campus Life, 1995-1996; Series 28 (Map-folder 3, Poster 4)
  - March Madness 2001, 2001 October 12; Series 28 (Map-folder 3, Poster 5)
  - Be Heard, 2002 February 4; Series 28 (Map-folder 3, Poster 6)
  - George Washington University Hospital Grand Opening, 2002 August 14; Series 28 (Map-folder 3, Poster 7)
  - Midnight Breakfast Safari, 2001 May 7; Series 28 (Box 3, Poster 1)
  - 2000 Fall Film Series, Series 28 (Box 3, Poster 2)
  - Festival of the Arts and Chalk-In 2002, 2002 April 12; Series 28 (Box 3, Poster 3)
  - I Know What You're Doing This Summer, undated; Series 28 (Box 3, Poster 4)
  - Homecoming '98, 1998 January 28 - February 1; Series 28 (Box 3, Poster 5)
  - Unity Week, 2002 March 1 - 9; Series 28 (Box 3, Poster 6)
  - GW Triple Play Kickoff Weekend, undated; Series 28 (Box 3, Poster 7)
  - Jerry Springer Mounted Picture, undated; Series 28 (Box 3, Poster 8)
  - Welcome Week 1998, Series 28 (Box 3, Poster 9)
  - Special Gameroom Events, undated; Series 28 (Box 3, Poster 10)
  - La Familia Latina (Hispanic Heritage Month 2002), Series 28 (Box 3, Poster 11)
  - Chalking the Campus, 1999 April 27; Series 28 (Box 3, Poster 12)
  - GW 2000: Expect the Impossible, Series 28 (Box 3, Poster 13)
  - Margaret Cho comedy night, 2002; Series 28 (Box 3, Poster 14)
  - Fine Art of Campus Life, 1997-1998; Series 28 (Box 3, Poster 15)
  - Midnight Breakfast: Midnight in Paradise, 2004 April 28; Series 28 (Box 4, Poster 1)
  - Stress-Free Zone, 2002 December 8 - 12; Series 28 (Box 4, Poster 2)
  - Grad Week 2004, 2004 May 8 - 13; Series 28 (Box 4, Poster 3)
  - Capture Grad Week 2003, 2003 May 10 - 15; Series 28 (Box 4, Poster 4)
  - Winter Welcome Week 2003, Series 28 (Box 4, Poster 5)
  - Faces of Religion Week, 2000 November 4 - 7; Series 28 (Box 4, Poster 6)
  - Stay Classy Seniors, undated; Series 28 (Box 4, Poster 7)
  - School Daze, Winter Welcome Week 2001, Series 28 (Box 4, Poster 8)
  - Make a Splash This Summer, undated; Series 28 (Box 4, Poster 9)
- Sigma Xi banners, RG0115 Series 29; 1 Linear foot (Flat box 1)
  This series consists of two banners from Sigma Xi. The materials have no attributable date range.
  - Special Game room Events [1/2], 12/09/1999-12/17/1999 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Special Game room Events [2/2], 12/09/1999-12/17/1999 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Exam Relief at J Street [1/2], 12/13/1999-12/20/1999 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Exam Relief at J Street [2/2], 12/13/1999-12/20/1999 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 1st Home Basketball Games! Battle of the "Georges" [1/2], 11/13/1999-11/16/1999 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 1st Home Basketball Games! Battle of the "Georges" [2/2], 11/13/1999-11/16/1999 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Pre-Season Chat with the Coaches - Come Meet Coach Penders & Coach McKeown [1/2], 11/12/1999 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Pre-Season Chat with the Coaches - Come Meet Coach Penders & Coach McKeown [2/2], 11/12/1999 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Stress-Free Zone [1/2], 12/08/1999-12/18/1999 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Stress-Free Zone [2/2], 12/08/1999-12/18/1999 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - BB&T Classic - Winter Hoop Fest [1/2], 12/04/1999 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - BB&T Classic - Winter Hoop Fest [2/2], 12/04/1999 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Midnight Breakfast, 12/08/1999 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - What Are You Doing After Graduation? [1/2], 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Welcome Week '99 - Swing Night with the Jitterbugs Swing Club [1/2], 08/26/1999 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Welcome Week '99 - Swing Night with the Jitterbugs Swing Club [2/2], 08/26/1999 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Welcome Week '99 - Comedy Night [1/2], 08/23/1999 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Welcome Week '99 - Comedy Night [2/2], 08/23/1999 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - The Four Tops in Concert, 10/16/1999 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Recreational Sports & Fitness Services, Fall [1/2], 1999 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Intramurals & Club Sports [1/2], 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Intramurals & Club Sports [2/2], 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - You Know the Music Spin with the Four Tops! [1/2], 10/16/1999 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - You Know the Music Spin with the Four Tops! [2/2], 10/16/1999 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Women's A-10 Tournament, 02/27/1999-03/01/1999 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Unity Week '99 - Margaret Cho [1/2], 03/09/1999 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Make a Splash This Summer!, 06/03/1999-08/06/1999 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Chalking the Campus 19th Annual Chalk-in [1/2], 04/27/199 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - DC's Promise for Youth Summit [1/2], 04/26/1999 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - International Week '99, Kaleidoscope, 04/08/1999-04/17/1999 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Accept the Challenge Student Leadership Conference, 04/27/1999 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Chalking the Campus 19th Annual Chalk-in [2/2], 04/27/1999 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - DC's Promise for Youth Summit [2/2], 04/26/1999 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - What Are You Doing After Graduation? [2/2], 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - The Comedy Show with Jon Stewart [1/2], 02/06/2000 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - The Comedy Show with Jon Stewart [2/2], 02/06/2000 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Thinking about Tomorrow '99: A Dialogue on Ethics, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Men's A-10 Tournament, 03/03/1999-03/06/1999 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Unity Week '99, Margaret Cho [2/2], 03/09/1999 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Spring Auditions for Cheerleaders, Dancers, and Mascots [1/2], 04/24/1999-05/05/1999 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Recreational Sports and Fitness Services [2/2], 11/1999 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Certificate of Membership, 04/30/1999 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Leadership, 1999 Student Leadership Conference [1/2], 10/03/1999 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Leadership, 1999 Student Leadership Conference [2/2], 10/03/1999 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Welcome Week '99 Yeah Baby Yeah! [1/2], 08/20/1999-08/29/1999 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Welcome Week '99 Yeah Baby Yeah [2/2], 08/20/1999-08/29/1999 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Tom & Jerry Winter Welcome Week '99, 01/10/1999-01/15/1999 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - GWU RSFS, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Midnight Breakfast, 05/08/2000 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - GW Triple Play Kickoff Weekend, 08/31/2000-09/02/2000 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Spring Auditions for Cheerleaders, Dancers, and Mascots [2/2], 04/24/1999-05/05/1999 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - The Event Formerly Known As Homecoming [1/2], 02/04/2000-02/06/2000 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - The Event Formerly Known As Homecoming [2/2], 02/04/2000-02/06/2000 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - We Are Going to Monopolyze Your Week [1/2], 01/18/2000-01/22/2000 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - We Are Going to Monopolyze Your Week [2/2], 01/18/2000-01/22/2000 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Welcome Week '99 Yeah Baby, Yeah (large poster) [1/2], 08/20/1999-08/29/1999 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Welcome Week '99 Yeah Baby, Yeah (large poster) [2/2], 08/20/1999-08/29/1999 (Box 1, Folder 57)
- Phi Beta Kappa, 1938-1988; RG0115 Series 30; 1 Linear foot (Box 1)
  This series consists of constitutions, handbooks, histories, etc. of the GW Phi Beta Kappa chapter. The materials range in date from 1938-88.
  - Information on the founding of the first chapter at GWU #, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Chapter Bi-Laws, Officer Manuals, Constitution, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Chapter Constitution, various versions, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Manual for Chapter Officers, Delegate's Manual, Handbook for New Members, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Phi Beta Kappa Pin and book "Insignia of Phi Beta Kappa", undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Fiftieth Anniversary Materials, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Banquets and Award Dinners: invitations, programs, magazine articles, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Negatives of people, undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Print Block of Phi Beta Kappa Charter, undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Campus posters, 1965-2004; RG0115 Series 31; 2 Linear feet (Box 1, Box 2)
  This series consists of a collection of campus posters of various activities and events (taking place at the Marvin Center, Lisner Auditorium, Dimock Gallery), including sports teams, film festivals, and convocations. The materials range in date from 1965-2004.
  - Women's Basketball, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Women's Basketball, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Women's Basketball, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Women's Basketball, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Women's Basketball - Colonials, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Women's Basketball, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Women's Basketball, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Women's Basketball, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Women's Basketball, 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - 25 Years of Atlantic 10 basketball, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Men's Basketball, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Men's Basketball, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    4 copies
  - Men's Basketball, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Men's Basketball, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Men's Basketball - Colonial, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Men's Basketball, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Men's Basketball - World Class Colonials, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Men's Basketball, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Men's Basketball, 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Men's Basketball, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Men's Basketball, 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - GW Men's Basketball Team Picture, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Newspaper tin plates of articles on GW's Basketball Team, 03/15/1993-03/22/1993 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Mens' Soccer, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Mens' Soccer, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Coca Cola Atlantic 10th Gymnast Championship, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Colonial Women's Volleyball, undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - GWU College Calendar with Advertisements and Discount Coupons, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - GWU College Calendar with Advertisements and Discount Coupons, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - GWU College Calendar with Advertisements and Discount Coupons, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - GWU College Calendar with Advertisements and Discount Coupons, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - GWU College Calendar with Advertisements and Discount Coupons, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - GWU College Calendar with Advertisements and Discount Coupons, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - GWU College Calendar with Advertisements and Discount Coupons, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Marvin Center:"Arms and The Man" By George Bernard Shaw - Oct 13-18, undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Marvin Center:"Ah Wilderness", "The Cranberry Tales", "The Serpent of Ai", "The Balcony" - GWU Speech and Drama Department, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Marvin Center:Summer Dance Workshop - Marta Renzi & Maida Withers, 06/01/1982-06/25/1982 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Marvin Center:"Blithe Spirit" - Feb 24-28, undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Marvin Center:What is Martha Marathon? - Feb 20, undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Marvin Center:GWU Dances - GWU Dance Chor., 1978 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Marvin Center:Tramp Art (Collection of H.I Gates & Sharie L. 05), 11/15/1976 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Marvin Center:Matteo: Indo American Dance Company - March, undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Marvin Center:Spring Concert: Univ. Singer Troubadours, 04/1990 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Marvin Center:Another Part of the Forest - Nov 4-9, undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Marvin Center:American College Theater Festival VII April 17-20, undated (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Marvin Center:"Bercht on Bercht", "Futz", "Little Mary Sunshine", "The Devils", undated (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Marvin Center:Stress Free Zone - Midnight Breakfast, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Marvin Center:Casino Games - Monte Carlo Night, 11/16/2000 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Marvin Center:Wooden Teeth - September 29, undated (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Marvin Center:Midnight Breakfast, 05/08/2000 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Marvin Center:Stress Free Zone, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Marvin Center:Homecoming Week, 02/04/2000-04/06/2000 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Marvin Center:French Quater Quartlet - March 26-31, undated (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Marvin Center:Theater 15th Season "Arms The Man", "Electra", "A Musical", "Dark of the Moon", "Company", 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Marvin Center:GWU Chamber Choir - "Troubadours" - November 2, undated (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Marvin Center:Moliere's "Tartuffe" - April 7-12, undated (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Marvin Center:Inaugural Ball for Bill Clinton, 01/20/1993 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Marvin Center:Chuck Berry and Bo Didley, May 9, undated (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Marvin Center:"Lock Up Your Daughters", Sept 30-Oct 6, undated (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Marvin Center:Martin Luther King, Jr. Birthday Celebration, 01/19/1987 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Marvin Center:Dance Concert, 12/03/1976-12/04/1976 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Marvin Center:Dance Concerts by GW dance Company, March 6-8, 13, 15, undated (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Marvin Center:Women of Manhattan, Feb 15-18, undated (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Marvin Center:"Lion of Winter " Oct 16-18, 23-25, undated (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Marvin Center:"Lysistrada" Oct 14-18, undated (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Marvin Center:Halloween Party, 10/29/1982 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Marvin Center:Washington Dance, 06/14/1984-06/16/1984 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Marvin Center:"A Shayna Maidel", 04/11/2002-04/14/2002 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Marvin Center:GWU Dance - Nov 30-Dec 1, undated (Box 2, Folder 42)
    Framed
  - Marvin Center:Spring Dance Concert, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Marvin Center:Israel Day, 04/26/2004 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Marvin Center:Get Pitch Slapped, All-Female acapella, 04/17/2004 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Lisner Auditorium:Human Evolution lectures, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Lisner Auditorium:10th Annual WFMA Benefit Concert, 01/2/1995 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Lisner Auditorium:Russ Freeman & The Rippingtons March 23, undated (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Lisner Auditorium:Boy George - Nov 16, undated (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Lisner Auditorium:Embassy of Egypt films, 10/10/1995-10/12/1995 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Lisner Auditorium:Maida Withers Dance Construction Company, 02/15/2001-02/16/2001 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Dimock Gallery: April 1-16, Faculty Hang Ups #2, undated (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Dimock Gallery: Edvard Munch, 12/15/1976-01/14/1977 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Dimock Gallery: An American Arch: Its Roots, Growth, & Horizon, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Dimock Gallery: GW Ceramics Program student show, 11/17/1976-11/29/1976 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Dimock Gallery: Herewood Lester Cooke, 10/29/1974-11/1/1974 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Dimock Gallery: Dance Event, Nov 13-14, undated (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Summer Film Festival - Lisner Auditorium, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Fall Film Festival - Lisner Auditorium, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Spring Film Festival - Lisner Auditorium, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - GWU Program Board Films Spring - Marvin Center, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Fall Film Festival, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - GWU Program Board Films Fall - Marvin Center, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - GWU Program Board Films Fall - Marvin Center, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - GWU Program Board Films Spring - Marvin Center, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - GWU Program Board Films Fall - Marvin Center, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - GWU Program Board Films Fall - Marvin Center, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - GWU Program Board Films Spring - Marvin Center, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - GWU Program Board Films Fall - Marvin Center, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - GWU Program Board Films Spring - Marvin Center, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - GWU Program Board Films Fall - Marvin Center, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Fall Film Festival - Marvin Center, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Nordic Film Festival, Gelman Library, 10/2003-12/2003 (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Fine Art of Campus Life, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Fine Art of Campus Life, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Fine Art of Campus Life, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Fine Art of Campus Life, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Fine Art of Campus Life, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Opening Convocation, 09/16/1981 (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - Opening Convocation, 09/14/1982 (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - Opening Convocation, 09/11/1992 (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - Colonial Convocation, 08/30/1993 (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - Univ. Honors Convocation, 04/14/1985 (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - Univ. Honors Convocation, 03/25/1988 (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - Univ. Honors Convocation, 04/1994 (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - Ambassadors Lecture Series - Fall 1993, undated (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - Ambassadors Lecture Series - Spring 1994, undated (Box 2, Folder 87)
  - International Week - World Mosaic, 04/10/1993-04/17/1993 (Box 2, Folder 88)
  - International Week - Discover the Treasures We Share, 04/3/1997-04/14/1997 (Box 2, Folder 89)
    2 cppies
  - Printing Impact on Man, 01/1978-02/1978 (Box 2, Folder 90)
  - Career Fair, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 91)
  - GW Summer Session, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 92)
  - GW 175th Capital Holiday - 19 December, undated (Box 2, Folder 93)
  - Alpha Kappa Alpha Sorority: Love Jones Cafe May 4, undated (Box 2, Folder 94)
  - Midnight Madness, undated (Box 2, Folder 95)
  - Welcome Week Aug 22 - Sept 3, undated (Box 2, Folder 96)
  - Festival of the Arts & Chalk In, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 97)
  - Recreational Sports, 11/1999 (Box 2, Folder 98)
  - March Madness, 03/2000 (Box 2, Folder 99)
  - Washington's Broadcast Legacy, 04/20/1998-05/29/1998 (Box 2, Folder 100)
  - Religion Week, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 101)
  - Health & Wellness Center grand opening, 08/29/2001 (Box 2, Folder 102)
  - Presidential Administrative Fellowship, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 103)
  - Celebrate the Inauguration, 01/20/2001 (Box 2, Folder 104)
  - "The Weaving of a Dream" "Leaving Home" Dance Dept. senior theses performances, 12/8/2000-12/9/2000 (Box 2, Folder 105)
  - GW Annual Holiday Party, 12/18/2000 (Box 2, Folder 106)
  - College Democrats Sept 19, undated (Box 2, Folder 107)
  - GW Mare Abraham, Lorraine Greenfield, 01/11/1999-03/12/1999 (Box 2, Folder 108)
  - Welcome Week, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 109)
  - Career Fair, 09/2000 (Box 2, Folder 110)
  - Homecoming, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 111)
  - "Global Rhythms" - International Week, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 112)
  - "Discover The Treasures We Share" - International Week, 04/3/1997-04/14/1997 (Box 2, Folder 113)
  - Seven Seconds 1993 Marc. C. Abrahams - GWU Colonnade Gallery, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 114)
  - GWU Summer School Scholar Program, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 115)
  - GWU Library: Photographia of the 19th Century, 10/3/1977-10/29/1977 (Box 2, Folder 116)
  - Broadside, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 117)
  - Women History Month, 03/2001 (Box 2, Folder 118)
  - The Intellectual Property and Patent Law Prog. "A Century of Excellence" Since 1891, undated (Box 2, Folder 119)
  - "Celebrate 90 Years in the Foggy Bottom" - Foggy Bottom Ball, 02/23/2002 (Box 2, Folder 120)
  - Bicentennial Summer of 1976 (Box 2, Folder 121)
  - Registration, Oct 31-Nov 11, undated (Box 2, Folder 122)
  - "George Calling" fundraising telethon,c.1985, undated (Box 2, Folder 123)
  - Spring Fling Party, 04/25/1982 (Box 2, Folder 124)
  - Celebrate Black History, Jan 21-Mar 1, undated (Box 2, Folder 125)
  - School of Government Commencement, 05/05/1985 (Box 2, Folder 126)
  - World in Motion, 04/04/1994-04/10/1994 (Box 2, Folder 127)
  - "Would you buy a car from this man?" (Impeach Nixon), c.1974, undated (Box 2, Folder 128)
  - Jay Leno, 10/12/2002 (Box 2, Folder 129)
  - Midnight Breakfast, 05/02/2002 (Box 2, Folder 130)
  - Martin Luther King, Jr. day convocation, 01/24/1994 (Box 2, Folder 131)
  - GW Seniors: Apply for the Presidential Administrative Fellowship, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 132)
  - "Looking Back...Moving Forward" (35th anniversary of 03 on Washington exhibit), 1998 (Box 2, Folder 133)
  - March on Washington (Gelman Special Collections exhibit poster of Lincoln Memorial), 08/23/1963 (Box 2, Folder 134)
  - Black History Celebration, 01/24/1998-04/25/1998 (Box 2, Folder 135)
  - Black History Celebration, 01/22/1996-03/9/1996 (Box 2, Folder 136)
  - GW's 13th Annual Holiday Gathering, 12/17/2002 (Box 2, Folder 137)
  - The Dream in Action, Convocation in Honor of Dr. Martin Luther King, Jr., 01/23/1996 (Box 2, Folder 138)
  - Capture Grad Week 2003, Student Activities Center (Box 2, Folder 139)
  - Midnight Breakfast, J Street and Hippodrome, 04/28/2004 (Box 2, Folder 140)
  - Globalization Week, Spring, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 141)
  - Asian South Asian Pacific Islander American Heritage Month events, 04/2004 (Box 2, Folder 142)
  - GWU montage of scenes in the form of the Rembrandt Peale portrait of George Washington, undated (Box 2, Folder 143)
    Gift of Class of 2002
- Office files, 1951-1971; RG0115 Series 32; 0.25 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series contains bulletins, memorandums, and rules. They range in date from 1951 to 1971. The materials concern regulations for student activities; registration and recognition of student organizations; and demonstration, rally, and assembly guidelines.
  - Student Activities Regulations, 06/1951-10/19/1971 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Omicron Delta Kappa records, 1929-2012; RG0115 Series 33; 1 Linear Feet 2 document boxes (Box 1, Box 2)
  The first box in this series contains Omicron Delta Kappa by-laws, minutes, applications, photos, reports, correspondence. They range in date from 1939-65.
  The second box contains a record book of members, minutes, finances, etc. 1929-1954, 1973; record book of initiation attendees and initiates,1982-2012; 80th anniversary recognition, 2009; initiation ceremony script, 2011-2012; flag, T-shirt and pins, circa 2012.
  Omicron Delta Kappa is a National leadership honor society for college students, faculty, staff, administrators, and alumni, and was chartered at George Washington University in 1929. The GW group is called the Alpha Delta Circle.
  The contents of Box 2 of this series were transferred to the archives by the Office of Student Engagement in 2017 (Accession 2017-045).
- Sigma Nu Delta Pi Chapter fraternity records, 2005-2007; Series 34; 5 item(s) 5 electronic documents
  This series contains five electronic documents. These documents tell a very small portion of the history of the Sigma Nu Delta Pi Chapter fraternity at GWU. There is a spreadsheet with financial data for a crispy creme fundraiser in 2006 and a document to review and revise the pledge procedure for the fraternity and formalize a brotherhood retreat.
  Although these documents do not reveal much history of the fraternity it is hopeful that more material will be donated in the future.
  These documents are available upon request.
  - Proposed Revisions: Pledge Process, undated; Series 34
  - Rav Packet, undated; Series 34
  - Running Shirts, undated; Series 34
  - Sigma Nu Finances Spring 2007 May 28, 05/28/2007; Series 34
  - Sigma Nu White Rose Formal Ballot, undated; Series 34
- Publications and Student Materials, Series 35
  - Newman Catholic Student Center Materials, 2006-2007; Series 35 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Student Planner, 2000-2001; Series 35 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Student Planner, 1993-1994; Series 35 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - The Delta of Sigma Nu, Fall 1989; Series 35 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - "Catch the Greek Fever", 2005; Series 35 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Student Organization Directory, 1992-1993; Series 35 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Philippine Cultural Society Materials, 2006-2012 (Box 1, Folder 7)